Guide to the Big Band Arrangements Collection, 1990-2017 SC.2017.01
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Big Band Arrangements, I.
  - Dry Bones (Ray Anthony) (Box 7, Folder 418)
  - Duke (Bob Florence) (Box 17, Folder 1058)
  - Dynaflow (Stan Kenton) (Box 28, Folder 2592)
  - Eager Beaver (Stan Kenton) (Box 4, Folder 234)
  - Eager Beaver (Stan Kenton) (Box 8, Folder 477)
  - East of the Sun (Les Elgart) (Box 8, Folder 512)
  - East of the Sun (Les Brown) (Box 15, Folder 938)
  - East of the Sun (Ray Anthony) (Box 23, Folder 2282)
  - Easy Living (Bill Holman) (Box 27, Folder 2514)
  - Easy Street (Billy May) (Box 11, Folder 670)
  - Easy to Love (Woody Herman) (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Easy to Love, Vocal (Box 6, Folder 372)
  - Easy to Love, Vocal (F) (Box 18, Folder 1162)
  - Easy to Remember (Ted Heath) (Box 15, Folder 906)
  - Eli is Coming (Count Basie) (Box 16, Folder 985)
  - Elks Parade (Box 24, Folder 2307)
  - Elmer's Time (The Modernaires) (Glenn Miller), Vocal Group (Box 9, Folder 555)
  - Elmer's Time (Glenn Miller) (Box 2, Folder 121)
  - Embraceable You (Ray Anthony) (Box 19, Folder 2016)
  - Embraceable You (Ray Anthony) (Box 21, Folder 2142)
  - Embraceable You (Ted Heath) (Box 22, Folder 2215)
  - End of a Love Affair (Stan Kenton) (Box 8, Folder 492)
  - Endless Love (Lionel Richie) (Box 15, Folder 974)
  - Enough on My Mind (Harry James) (Box 18, Folder 1151)
  - Ernie's Blues (Ray Anthony) (Box 19, Folder 1188)
  - Evergreen, Vocal (A to C) (Box 10, Folder 631)
  - Every Day I Have the Blues, Vocal (F) (Box 21, Folder 2151)
  - Every Time We Say Goodbye (Stan Kenton) (Box 13, Folder 820)
  - Every Tub (Count Basie) (Box 21, Folder 2148)
  - Everybody Loves Somebody (Woody Herman) (Box 26, Folder 2427)
  - Everybody Loves Somebody, Vocal (Eb) (Box 26, Folder 2443)
  - Exactly Like You, Vocal (Bb-C) (Box 20, Folder 2100)
  - Falling in Love (Ernie Wilkins) (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Falling in Love with Love, Vocal (G) (Box 9, Folder 550)
  - Falling Leaves (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 141)
  - Fan It Janet (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 13, Folder 804)
  - Fantail (Count Basie) (Box 25, Folder 2391)
  - Far Down Under (Bill Holman) (Box 19, Folder 1070)
  - Fat Man Boogie (Billy May) (Box 17, Folder 1057)
  - Feelings, Vocal (Eb) (Box 8, Folder 450)
  - Fever (Box 21, Folder 2141)
  - Fifth of Beethoven (Stan Kenton) (Box 6, Folder 377)
  - Filet of Soul (Woody Herman) (Box 28, Folder 2569)
  - Fire and Rain (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 17, Folder 1082)
  - Five Brothers (Woody Herman) (Box 16, Folder 1030)
  - Flamingo (Sam Donahue) (Box 8, Folder 488)
  - Flamingo (Box 17, Folder 1092)
  - Flat Bush Flanagan (Harry James) (Box 7, Folder 403)
  - Flight of the Foo Birds (Count Basie) (Box 16, Folder 1035)
  - Fly Me to the Moon, Vocal (Bb) (Box 23, Folder 2256)
  - Fly Me to the Moon (Eydie Gormé), Vocal (C) (Box 25, Folder 2358)
  - Fly Me to the Moon, Vocal (C) (Box 25, Folder 2359)
  - Flying Home (Benny Goodman) (Box 20, Folder 2072)
  - Flying Home (Lionel Hampton) (Box 26, Folder 2423)
  - Folks That Live on the Hill (Ted Heath) (Box 7, Folder 397)
  - Foo Birds (Box 11, Folder 692)
  - Fools Rush In, Vocal (F) (Box 9, Folder 539)
  - For Dancers Only (Ray Anthony) (Box 4, Folder 238)
  - For Once in My Life, Vocal (Bb) (Box 27, Folder 2480)
  - For Once in My Lifetime (Box 24, Folder 2340)
  - For Once in My Lifetime (Box 19, Folder 2007)
  - For Sentimental Reasons, Vocal (Db) (Box 25, Folder 2384)
  - For Sentimental Reasons, Vocal (Bb to B) (Box 4, Folder 235)
  - Forever in Love (Box 23, Folder 2275)
  - Forever in Love (Kenny G) (Box 14, Folder 883)
  - Four Brothers (Woody Herman) (Box 9, Folder 534)
  - Four Others (Woody Herman) (Box 15, Folder 946)
  - Fours (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 18, Folder 1159)
  - Frame for the Blues (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 2, Folder 91)
  - French Foreign Legion (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 21, Folder 2105)
  - Frenesi (Artie Shaw) (Box 15, Folder 947)
  - Frenesi (Glenn Miller) (Box 17, Folder 1067)
  - From This Moment, Vocal (Eb) (Box 18, Folder 1155)
  - From This Moment On (Les Brown) (Box 9, Folder 521)
  - Fugetta (Bob Florence) (Box 2, Folder 87)
  - Funky Serenade (Terry Gibbs) (Box 10, Folder 633)
  - Funny How Time Slips Away, Vocal (F) (Box 27, Folder 2523)
  - Games That People Play, Vocal (E) (Box 21, Folder 2163)
  - Gene's Boogie (Gene Krupa) (Box 15, Folder 945)
  - Georgia On My Mind (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 181)
  - Georgia On My Mind (Les Elgart) (Box 24, Folder 2343)
  - Get It On (Box 19, Folder 2027)
  - Get Me to the Church on Time (Les Brown) (Box 15, Folder 911)
  - Getting Out (Chicago) (Box 27, Folder 2515)
  - Ghost of a Chance (Les Brown) (Box 3, Folder 137)
  - Gimme a Litle Kiss (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (G) (Box 25, Folder 2364)
  - Gina (Box 9, Folder 531)
  - Glad You're You (The Four Freshmen) (Billy May), Vocal Group (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - God Bless the Child, Vocal (G) (Box 18, Folder 1135)
  - Going Out of My Head (Box 22, Folder 2180)
  - Gonna Fly Now (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 2, Folder 82)
  - Good Morning Heartaches, Vocal (Eb) (Box 18, Folder 1112)
  - Goodbye (Benny Goodman) (Box 20, Folder 2099)
  - Goodbye Yesterday (Buddy Rich) (Box 16, Folder 1034)
  - Goodman Medley (Box 14, Folder 881)
  - Goodnight Sweetheart (Ralph Marterie) (Box 9, Folder 591)
  - Goody, Goody, Vocal (G) (Box 7, Folder 399)
  - Got a Date with an Angel (Hal Kemp) (Box 5, Folder 292)
  - Grand Street (Count Basie) (Box 22, Folder 2214)
  - Grand Street (Count Basie) (Sonny Rollins) (Box 24, Folder 2300)
  - Gravy Waltz (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 24, Folder 2286)
  - Gravy Waltz (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 26, Folder 2409)
  - Greasy Sack Blues (Woody Herman) (Box 21, Folder 2133)
  - Green Dolphin Street (Glenn Miller) (Box 2, Folder 108)
  - Green Dolphin Street (Box 14, Folder 847)
  - Green Eyes, Vocal (C to F) (Box 3, Folder 187)
  - Green Onions (Box 11, Folder 697)
  - Green Onions (Box 23, Folder 2273)
  - Groovin' Hard (Buddy Rich) (Box 15, Folder 943)
  - Groundhog (Duke Parsons) (Box 16, Folder 1003)
  - Group Shot (Buddy Rich) (Box 18, Folder 1029)
  - Guantanamera (Box 7, Folder 428)
  - Guilty, Vocal (Bb) (Box 29, Folder 3313)
  - Gumshoe (Count Basie) (Box 13, Folder 838)
  - Gypsie in My Soul, Vocal (Bb) (Box 27, Folder 2503)
  - Gypsie in My Soul, Vocal (B to Bb) (Box 29, Folder 2601)
  - Hamp's Boogie (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Handful of Stars (Glenn Miller) (Box 10, Folder 636)
  - Happiness (Terry Gibbs) (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Happiness is Just a Thing Called Joe (Terry Gibbs) (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Happiness is Just a Thing Called Joe (Woody Herman) (Box 14, Folder 898)
  - Happy Talk (The Four Freshmen), Vocal Group (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Harbor Lights (Box 24, Folder 2319)
  - Harlem Airshaft (Duke Ellington) (Box 25, Folder 2357)
  - Harlem Nocturne (Box 3, Folder 192)
  - Harlem Nocturne (Ray Anthony) (Box 13, Folder 779)
  - Harlem Nocturne (Box 19, Folder 2015)
  - Harry James Medley (Box 24, Folder 2322)
  - Harry, not Jesse (Harry James) (Box 21, Folder 2111)
  - Hava Nagila (Box 20, Folder 2049)
  - Have You Met Miss Jones (Les Brown) (Box 6, Folder 365)
  - Hawaiian War Chant (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 8, Folder 447)
  - Hawaiian Wedding Song (Box 10, Folder 621)
  - Heart and Soul (Ray Conniff) (Box 15, Folder 954)
  - Heartaches (Box 25, Folder 2356)
  - Heavy Blues (Woody Herman) (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Hello, Dolly (Bobby Darin) (Box 24, Folder 2302)
  - Hello, I Love You (Buddy Rich) (Box 16, Folder 1028)
  - Help Me Make it Through the Night (Box 15, Folder 927)
  - Help Me Make it Through the Night, Vocal (C) (Box 25, Folder 2363)
  - Here Comes Charlie (Charlie Barnet) (Box 6, Folder 366)
  - Here There and Everywhere (Count Basie) (Box 18, Folder 1139)
  - Here We Go Again (Glenn Miller) (Box 21, Folder 2143)
  - Here's That Rainy Day (Box 9, Folder 556)
  - Here's That Rainy Day (Urbie Green) (Box 13, Folder 799)
  - Here's That Rainy Day (Stan Kenton) (Box 17, Folder 1158)
  - Hernando's Hideaway (Box 22, Folder 2194)
  - Hey Daddy (Glenn Miller), Vocal Band (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Hey Daddy (Sammy Kay) (Box 5, Folder 285)
  - Hey Daddy (Glenn Miller), Vocal Band (Box 17, Folder 1075)
  - Hey Jealous Lover (Count Basie) (Box 6, Folder 340)
  - Hey Jealous Lover (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 28, Folder 2557)
  - Hey Jude (Maynard Ferguson) (Box 2, Folder 85)
  - Hey There (Nancy Wilson), Vocal (Bb) (Box 15, Folder 917)
  - High Noon (Billy May) (Box 11, Folder 671)
  - High on a Windy Trumpet (Les Brown) (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Home (Glenn Miller) (Box 4, Folder 231)
  - Honeysuckle Rose, Vocal (Bb) (Box 25, Folder 2395)
  - Honeysuckle Rose (Terry Gibbs) (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Hot Toddy (Box 25, Folder 206)
  - House Party (Ray Anthony) (Box 16, Folder 786)
  - How About You, Vocal (F) (Box 29, Folder 2630)
  - How Deep is the Ocean (Stan Kenton) (Box 9, Folder 542)
  - How Deep is the Ocean (Harry James) (Box 9, Folder 571)
  - How Deep is Your Love (Box 5, Folder 265)
  - How Do You Keep the Music Playing (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 25, Folder 2400)
  - How High the Moon (Les Brown) (Box 4, Folder 203)
  - How High the Moon, Vocal (Eb) (Box 17, Folder 1096)
  - How High the Moon (Box 23, Folder 2252)
  - How High the Moon, Vocal (Eb) (Box 29, Folder 2612)
  - How Little We Know (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 23, Folder 2239)
  - How Little We Know, Vocal (F) (Box 26, Folder 2452)
  - How Now Brown Cow (Les Brown) (Box 12, Folder 753)
  - I Am What I Am (Connie Stevens), Vocal (F) (Box 12, Folder 751)
  - I Believe in Music, Vocal (Eb) (Box 13, Folder 831)
  - I Can't Believe You're in Love (Les Brown) (Box 15, Folder 919)
  - I Can't Get Started (Bunny Berigan) (Box 3, Folder 135)
  - I Can't Get Started (Box 9, Folder 577)
  - I Can't Begin to Tell You (Harry James) (Box 23, Folder 2271)
  - I Can't Give You Anything but Love (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 27, Folder 2498)
  - I Can't Stop Lovin' You (Count Basie) (Box 4, Folder 245)
  - I Concentrate on You, Vocal (C) (Box 12, Folder 762)
  - I Concentrate on You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 27, Folder 2497)
  - I Concentrate on You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 28, Folder 2546)
  - I Concentrate on You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (C) (Box 28, Folder 2531)
  - I Could Have Danced (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 688)
  - I Could Have Danced All Night (Les Brown) (Box 14, Folder 872)
  - I Could Have Danced All Night (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 26, Folder 2411)
  - I Could Have Danced All Night, Vocal (Ab) (Box 21, Folder 2147)
  - I Could Write a Book (Les Brown) (Box 12, Folder 770)
  - I Cover the Waterfront (Artie Shaw) (Box 21, Folder 2155)
  - I Cover the Waterfront, Vocal (Db) (Box 12, Folder 740)
  - I Cried for You (Harry James) (Box 2, Folder 118)
  - I Didn't Know What Time It Was, Vocal (Eb) (Box 16, Folder 1010)
  - I Don't Know Why (Les Elgart) (Box 9, Folder 559)
  - I Don't Know Why (Ray Anthony) (Box 20, Folder 2065)
  - I Don't Want to Walk Without You (Harry James) (Box 3, Folder 142)
  - I Don't Get Around Much Anymore (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 28, Folder 2506)
  - I Dream of You (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 17, Folder 1038)
  - I Dream of You, Vocal (C) (Box 23, Folder 2244)
  - I Dreamt I Dwelt in Harlem (Glenn Miller) (Box 6, Folder 374)
  - I Fall to Pieces (Patsy Cline), Vocal (C) (Box 22, Folder 2202)
  - I Feel Lucky (Pat Benatar), Vocal (A) (Box 29, Folder 2613)
  - I Feel the Earth Move (Box 19, Folder 2029)
  - I Found a New Baby (Lena Horne), Vocal (C) (Box 21, Folder 1121)
  - I Found a New Baby (Nancy Wilson), Vocal (C) (Box 21, Folder 2103)
  - I Get a Kick Out of You, Vocal (C) (Box 11, Folder 718)
  - I Get a Kick Out of You (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 17, Folder 1036)
  - I Get a Kick Out of You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Db) (Box 20, Folder 2077)
  - I Get a Kick Out of You, Vocal (Eb) (Box 26, Folder 2460)
  - I Get a Kick Out of You (Ray Anthony) (Box 27, Folder 2519)
  - I Get a Kick Out of You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 28, Folder 2553)
  - I Get the Blues When It Rains (Lena Horne), Vocal (Box 18, Folder 1122)
  - I Got It Bad (Duke Ellington) (Box 6, Folder 327)
  - I Got Rhythm (Lena Horne), Vocal (Eb) (Box 18, Folder 1123)
  - I Had the Craziest Dream (Harry James) (Box 2, Folder 109)
  - I Hadn't Anyone 'Till You, Vocal (C) (Box 4, Folder 226)
  - I Hadn't Anyone 'Till You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 26, Folder 2413)
  - I Hear a Rhapsody (Glenn Miller) (Box 8, Folder 489)
  - I Just Called to Say I Love You (Box 16, Folder 980)
  - I Just Found Out About Love (Count Basie) (Box 21, Folder 2110)
  - I Know Why (Ray Anthony), Group Vocal (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - I Know Why (Glenn Miller) (Box 8, Folder 466)
  - I Let a Song Go Out of My Heart (Duke Ellington) (Box 18, Folder 1161)
  - I Like the Likes of You, (Vocal Ab) (Box 6, Folder 334)
  - I Love a Piano, (Vocal Bb) (Box 7, Folder 386)
  - I Love Paris (Woody Herman) (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - I Love You, (Vocal D) (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - I Love You (Billy May) (Box 14, Folder 875)
  - I Married an Angel (Ted Heath) (Box 6, Folder 357)
  - I Married an Angel (Ted Heath) (Box 6, Folder 363)
  - I May be Wrong (Gene Krupa) (Box 20, Folder 2062)
  - I Never Been in Love Before (Stan Kenton) (Box 19, Folder 1176)
  - I Only Have Eyes for You (Box 5, Folder 269)
  - I Only Have Eyes for You (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 719)
  - I Only Have Eyes for You (Glenn Miller) (Box 16, Folder 1017)
  - I Only Have Eyes for You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (F) (Box 26, Folder 2419)
  - I Only Have Eyes for You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 27, Folder 2471)
  - I Remember April (Les Elgart) (Box 23, Folder 2242)
  - I Remember You (Bill Holman) (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - I Remember You (Les Brown) (Box 3, Folder 171)
  - I Remember You (Les Brown), Vocal (Bb) (Box 8, Folder 465)
  - I Should Care, Vocal (Bb) (Box 14, Folder 893)
  - I Surrender Dear (Box 17, Folder 1072)
  - I Thought About You, Vocal (C) (Box 27, Folder 2504)
  - I Thought About You (The Four Freshmen), Vocal Group (Box 10, Folder 632)
  - I Thought About You (The Four Freshmen), Vocal Group (Box 17, Folder 1039)
  - I Understand (Stan Kenton) (Box 7, Folder 417)
  - I Wanna Be Around, Vocal (Ab) (Box 20, Folder 2092)
  - I Want a Sunday Kind of Love (Claude Thornhill) (Box 8, Folder 498)
  - I Want to Be Happy, Vocal (G) (Box 20, Folder 2054)
  - I Wish You Love (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Eb) (Box 10, Folder 649)
  - I'll Be Seeing You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (C) (Box 19, Folder 1166)
  - I'll Be Seeing You (Box 22, Folder 2220)
  - I'll Be Seeing You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 23, Folder 2227)
  - I'll Be Seeing You (Tommy Dorsey) (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Box 23, Folder 2259)
  - I'll Buy That Dream (Harry James) (Box 3, Folder 159)
  - I'll Close My Eyes (Ted Heath) (Box 8, Folder 513)
  - I'll Get By, Vocal (Ab) (Box 23, Folder 2245)
  - I'll Never Smile Again (Glenn Miller) (Box 14, Folder 882)
  - I'll Never Smile Again (Count Basie) (Box 14, Folder 889)
  - I'll Never Smile Again (Box 22, Folder 2221)
  - I'll Never Smile Again (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 22, Folder 2181)
  - I'll Remember April (Les Elgart) (Box 23, Folder 2229)
  - I'll Remember April (Les Elgart) (Box 26, Folder 2448)
  - I'll String Along With You (Box 27, Folder 2466)
  - I'll Take Romance, Vocal (C to Eb) (Box 2, Folder 92)
  - I'll Take Romance (Bill Holman) (Box 20, Folder 2086)
  - I'll Take Romance (Box 25, Folder 2361)
  - I'll Walk Alone, Vocal (F) (Box 17, Folder 1076)
  - I'll Wind (Woody Herman) (Box 26, Folder 2454)
  - I'm Getting Sentimental Over You (Box 3, Folder 167)
  - I'm Glad There Is You (Stan Kenton) (Box 9, Folder 566)
  - I'm Gonna Live 'Till I Die, Vocal (Db) (Box 5, Folder 270)
  - I'm Old Fashioned (Glenn Miller) (Box 17, Folder 1145)
  - I'm Sitting On Top of the World (Woody Herman), Vocal (Box 26, Folder 2464)
  - I'm Thrilled (Glenn Miller) (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - I'm Yours (Stan Kenton) (Box 3, Folder 127)
  - I'm Yours, Vocal (Box 26, Folder 2447)
  - I've Found a New Baby (Pete Fountain) (Box 27, Folder 2520)
  - I've Got a Crush on You (Linda Ronstadt), Vocal (C) (Box 14, Folder 878)
  - I've Got a Feeling I'm Falling (Ted Heath) (Box 14, Folder 903)
  - I've Got the Right to Sing the Blues, Vocal (F) (Box 18, Folder 1101)
  - I've Got the World on a String, Vocal (Box 11, Folder 677)
  - I've Got the World on a String (Box 22, Folder 2224)
  - I've Got the World on a String (Ted Heath) (Box 9, Folder 568)
  - I've Got the World on a String, Vocal (D) (Box 24, Folder 2314)
  - I've Got to Be Me, Vocal (Box 9, Folder 583)
  - I've Got You Under My Skin, Vocal (Bb) (Box 12, Folder 737)
  - I've Got You Under My Skin (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 20, Folder 2091)
  - I've Got You Under My Skin, Vocal (Eb) (Box 29, Folder 3318)
  - I've Heard That Song Before (Harry James) (Box 11, Folder 714)
  - I've Heard that Song Before (Urbie Green) (Box 13, Folder 792)
  - I've Never Been in Love Before (Box 20, Folder 2064)
  - Ida (Glenn Miller) (Box 4, Folder 219)
  - Ida (Ray Anthony) (Box 14, Folder 857)
  - If I Could Be With You (Box 12, Folder 743)
  - If I Had You (Ray Anthony) (Box 10, Folder 644)
  - If I Had You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 28, Folder 2561)
  - If I Should Lose You, Vocal (Ab) (Box 13, Folder 789)
  - If I Should Lose You (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Ab) (Box 26, Folder 2420)
  - If I Sing You a Love Song (Box 10, Folder 638)
  - If She Walked into My Life (Box 3, Folder 129)
  - If You Were the Only Girl, Vocal (G) (Box 29, Folder 3316)
  - Imagination, Vocal (Ab) (Box 10, Folder 600)
  - Imagination (Glenn Miller) (Box 15, Folder 926)
  - Imagination, Vocal Group (Box 26, Folder 2430)
  - Imagination (Woody Herman) (Box 26, Folder 2463)
  - Imagination (The Four Freshmen) (Stan Kenton), Vocal Group (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - In a Little Spanish Town (Box 7, Folder 407)
  - In a Mellow Tone (Buddy Rich) (Box 3, Folder 151)
  - In a Mellow Tone (Ralph Marterie) (Box 13, Folder 834)
  - In a Mellow Tone (Box 9, Folder 573)
  - In an Old Fashioned Way, Vocal (G) (Box 22, Folder 2201)
  - In a Persian Market (Larry Clinton) (Box 6, Folder 381)
  - In a Sentimental Mood (Duke Ellington) (Box 5, Folder 259)
  - In a Sentimental Mood (Box 22, Folder 2213)
  - In a Sentimental Mood (Box 25, Folder 2397)
  - In a Sentimental Mood (Bill Holman) (Box 27, Folder 2511)
  - In an Old Fashioned Way (Box 3, Folder 174)
  - In Crowd (Quincy Jones) (Box 9, Folder 557)
  - In My Solitude (Box 22, Folder 2197)
  - In the Mood (Glenn Miller) (Box 4, Folder 233)
  - In the Mood (Ray Anthony) (Box 13, Folder 826)
  - In the Mood (Doc Severinsen) (Box 22, Folder 2204)
  - In the Still of Night, Vocal (C) (Box 9, Folder 554)
  - In the Still of Night (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Eb) (Box 28, Folder 2571)
  - Indian Summer (Glenn Miller) (Box 3, Folder 147)
  - Indian Summer (Les Brown) (Box 5, Folder 312)
  - Intermission Riff (Box 4, Folder 230)
  - Intermission Riff (Box 29, Folder 3329)
  - Intro to an Ending (Charlie Barnet) (Box 17, Folder 1095)
  - Invitation (Les Brown) (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Invitation (Buddy Morrow) (Tommy Dorsey) (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Ipanema, Vocal (F) (Box 15, Folder 914)
  - Isle of Capri (Box 7, Folder 437)
  - Isn't It Romantic (Billy May) (Box 5, Folder 301)
  - It Could Happen to You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 8, Folder 463)
  - It Could Happen to You, Vocal (Bb) (Box 12, Folder 734)
  - It Could Happen to You (Urbie Green) (Box 13, Folder 778)
  - It Don't Mean a Thing (Duke Ellington), Vocal (Eb) (Box 22, Folder 2173)
  - It Had to Be You, Vocal (C) (Box 18, Folder 1156)
  - It Had to Be You, Vocal (F) (Box 29, Folder 3323)
  - It Happened in Sun Valley (The Modernaires) (Glenn Miller), Vocal Group (Box 13, Folder 823)
  - It Might As Well Be Spring (Terry Gibbs), Vocal Group (Box 15, Folder 951)
  - It Must Be Jelly (Glenn Miller) (Box 12, Folder 729)
  - It's a Pity to Say Goodnight, Vocal (F) (Box 14, Folder 883)
  - It's a Pity to Say Goodnight, Vocal (F) (Box 15, Folder 970)
  - It's a Wonderful World, Vocal (F) (Box 9, Folder 562)
  - It's a Wonderful World (Woody Herman) (Box 13, Folder 828)
  - It's Been a Long Time (Harry James) (Box 8, Folder 508)
  - It's Callin' Time (Al Cohn) (Box 15, Folder 959)
  - It's All Right With Me (Box 10, Folder 602)
  - It's All Right With Me (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (C) (Box 25, Folder 2402)
  - It's Not Unusual (Les Brown) (Box 10, Folder 611)
  - It's Sand Man (Count Basie) (Box 24, Folder 2323)
  - It's Sand Man (Count Basie) (Box 24, Folder 2336)
  - It's You or No One (Les Brown) (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Italian Waltz Medley (Box 5, Folder 306)
  - Ja-Da (Ted Heath) (Box 14, Folder 894)
  - Ja-Da (Terry Gibbs) (Box 17, Folder 1061)
  - Jamaican Rhumba (Ralph Marterie) (Box 17, Folder 1063)
  - James Session (Harry James) (Box 27, Folder 2483)
  - Java (Box 24, Folder 2306)
  - Jazz Me Blues (Box 10, Folder 619)
  - Jazz Sonata (Oliver Nelson) (Box 18, Folder 2114)
  - Jeep Jockey Jump (Glenn Miller) (Box 21, Folder 2134)
  - Jeepers Creepers, Vocal (Ab) (Box 27, Folder 2472)
  - Jeeps Blues (Count Basie) (Box 27, Folder 2521)
  - Jersey Bouce (Benny Goodman) (Box 11, Folder 710)
  - Jessica's Day (Count Basie) (Box 25, Folder 2348)
  - Jingle Bells (Glenn Miller) (Box 13, Folder 780)
  - Jingle, Jangle, Jingle, Vocal (Eb) (Box 24, Folder 2236)
  - Johnson Rag (Glenn Miller) (Box 4, Folder 204)
  - Johnson Rag (Les Brown) (Box 15, Folder 918)
  - Johnson Rag (Box 21, Folder 2158)
  - Jukebox Saturday Night (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Eb) (Box 5, Folder 275)
  - Jump, Jive, and Wail (Box 20, Folder 2069)
  - Jumpin' at the Woodside (Count Basie) (Box 21, Folder 2117)
  - Jumptown (Harry James) (Box 28, Folder 2594)
  - Jungle Drums (Artie Shaw) (Box 13, Folder 829)
  - Just a Closer Walk With Thee (Box 22, Folder 2208)
  - Just a Gigolo (Box 7, Folder 413)
  - Just a Gigolo/I Ain't Got Nobody (David Lee Roth), Vocal (G) (Box 28, Folder 2532)
  - Just Basie (Count Basie) (Box 13, Folder 839)
  - Just Friends (Box 20, Folder 2019)
  - Just In Time (Les Elgart) (Box 11, Folder 691)
  - Just In Time (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 19, Folder 2031)
  - Just One More Chance (Box 17, Folder 1054)
  - Just One of Those Things (Box 25, Folder 2368)
  - Just One of Those Things, Vocal (Ab) (Box 15, Folder 967)
  - Just You, Just Me (Jack Jones), Vocal (Ab) (Box 25, Folder 2396)
  - Kalamazoo (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Ab) (Box 14, Folder 888)
  - Kansas City, Vocal (Bb) (Box 9, Folder 547)
  - Kansas City (Box 19, Folder 1183)
  - Kansas City, Vocal (Bb) (Box 22, Folder 2200)
  - Keen and Peachy (Woody Herman) (Box 7, Folder 425)
  - Keep 'em Flying (Ella Fitzgerald) (Glenn Miller), Vocal (Ab) (Box 22, Folder 2171)
  - Kerry Dance (Ray Anthony) (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Kid from Redbank (Count Basie) (Box 8, Folder 487)
  - Kind of Like the Blues (Harry James) (Box 13, Folder 797)
  - King Porter Stomp (Benny Goodman) (Box 8, Folder 462)
  - King Size Blues (Harry James) (Box 11, Folder 682)
  - Kiss of Fire (Box 29, Folder 2622)
  - Kiss to Build a Dream On, Vocal (Bb) (Box 24, Folder 2321)
  - Knock Three Times (Box 22, Folder 2209)
  - La Bamba (Les Brown) (Box 11, Folder 698)
  - La Bamba (Box 23, Folder 2280)
  - La Borrachita (Box 3, Folder 197)
  - La Cumparsita (Box 29, Folder 2619)
  - Lady (Box 22, Folder 2195)
  - Lady is a Tramp (Ted Heath) (Box 4, Folder 210)
  - Lady is a Tramp (Box 20, Folder 2043)
  - Lady is a Tramp (Frank Sinatra), Vocal (Bb) (Box 20, Folder 2088)
  - Lady is a Tramp, Vocal (G) (Box 23, Folder 2246)
  - Lady is a Tramp (Jack Jones), Vocal (C) (Box 27, Folder 2507)
  - Lambada (Box 21, Folder 2161)
  - Last Cheat'r's Waltz (Dean Kincaid) (Box 29, Folder 3330)
  - Late Date (Count Basie) (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Late in the Evening, Vocal (F) (Box 14, Folder 887)
  - Latin Flight (Woody Herman) (Box 8, Folder 509)
  - Laura (Box 6, Folder 342)
  - Laura (Ray Anthony) (Box 21, Folder 2121)